Guide to the James Buchanan Duke Papers, 1777-1990 and undated
James Buchanan Duke papers 1777-1990 and undated
- Legal Papers Series, 1878-1926 and undated (bulk 1910s-1925)
  Property deeds and transactions, wills, indentures, and records for the divorce of James B. Duke from Lillian N. Duke (1906) form the bulk of this series. In 1925 Lillian N. Duke appealed the divorce and the case was heard by the New York Supreme Court. The series includes copies of records from the original divorce case as well as records from the appeal in 1925. Arranged by subject, then chronologically.
  - Agreements, court records, indentures, 1897-1925 (Box 12)
  - Deeds and land plats, 1878-1924
  - Property and Houses:
    - Appraisals/Inventories, 1918, 1925-1926, undated
    - Somerville, N.J., deed, 1916
    - East 85th St., New York, N.Y., 1906-1912
    - 1 East 78th Street, New York, N.Y., 1913
    - 1009 Fifth Ave., New York, N.Y., 1901-1919, undated
    - Charlotte, N.C., 1917-1925
    - Durham, N.C., 1878-1907
  - Estate of Elizabeth L. Roney, 1882-1884, undated (Box 13)
  - On Petition for Divorce, Final Decree, 1906, May 7
  - Lillian N. Duke v. James B. Duke, 1925 (James B. Duke v. Lillian N. Duke, 1906):
    - Correspondence, 1925-1926
    - Court records:
      - Published, 1925
      - 1925
      - Exhibits, 1905-1906, 1925
      - Memorandum, 1907, 1925, undated
    - Research, 1925
    - Miscellaneous, 1925, undated
  - Indenture and Deed of Trust establishing The Doris Duke Trust, 1924, Dec. 11; additions, 1925, Oct. 23
  - Last Will and Testament and Codicil of James B. Duke, 1924-1925
- Financial Papers Series, 1874-1933 and undated (bulk 1900s-1925)
  Includes ledger books, journals, cashbooks, voucher records, deposit slips, cancelled checks, stock certificates, account balance worksheets, and expense records for payroll and other costs in the Duke households and offices, including The Duke Endowment. Some miscellaneous business records are scattered throughout. There are orders, invoices and receipts for jewelry, travel, club memberships, automobiles, and other expenses. See also oversize materials. Arranged in descending order according to the hierarchy of the bookkeeping system, followed by miscellaneous financial records and subject folders.
  - Ledger No. 1, 1890-1901 (Box 13)
  - Ledgers: (Box 14)
    - No. 2, 1902-1912
    - No. 3, 1913-1914
    - No. 4, 1915-1920
  - Ledger No. 5, 1920-1925 (Box 15)
  - Journals:
    - No. 1, 1890, Dec.-1905
    - No. 2, 1906, Jan.-1912
  - Journals: (Box 16)
    - No. 3, 1912, Dec.-1914
    - No. 4, 1915, Jan.-1919
    - No. 5, 1920, Jan.-1925, Oct.
  - Cashbooks: (Box 17)
    - No. 1, 1890, Dec.-1901, Nov.
    - No. 2, 1902, Jan.-1912, Apr.
    - No. 3, 1912, May-1914, Dec.
  - Cashbooks: (Box 18)
    - No. 4, 1915, Jan.-1918, July
    - No. 5, 1918, Aug.-1922, Apr.
    - No. 6, 1922, May-1925, Oct.
  - Voucher Records: (Ovolume Voucher Records 1-7. Shelved in the library stacks; please see the reference staff.)
    - No. 1, 1914, May-Dec.
    - No. 2, 1915, Jan.-1917, June
    - No. 3, 1917, June-1919, Jan.
    - No. 4, 1919, Feb.-1921, Apr.
    - No. 5, 1921, May-1923, May
    - No. 6, 1923, June-1925, Feb.
    - No. 7, 1925, Mar.-Oct.
  - Cancelled Checks: (Box 19)
    - Bankers Trust Co., 1916, Mar. 30-1925, July 10 (2 folders)
    - Farmers' Loan and Trust Co., 1894, Oct. 15-1909, Aug. 9 (4 folders)
  - Cancelled Checks: (Box 20)
    - Farmers' Loan and Trust Co., 1909, Sept. 2-1924, May 8 (2 folders)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. of New York, 1912, Jan. 19-1925, June 29 (3 folders)
    - National Bank of Commerce, 1914, Feb. 25-1925, June 9
    - National City Bank of New York, 1922, Jan. 7-1925, Sept. 2
    - Passbooks, 1907-1919
  - Deposit Slip Registers, 1918, July-1922, June (2 vols.) (Box 21)
  - Payroll and other expenses, 1917-1928 (2 vols.) (Includes Estate of James B. Duke and The Duke Endowment) (Box 22)
  - Employee Certificates of Residency, N.Y. State Income Tax, 1921-1927 (Box 23)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1920-1925 (6 folders)
  - State Income Taxes, 1922-1926
  - Miscellaneous receipts, etc., 1878-1908 (7 folders)
  - Miscellaneous receipts, etc., 1909-1925, undated, (6 folders) (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous financial statements of James B. Duke, 1913-1925, undated
  - Trial Balances, 1898-1900
  - Subject folders/Charitable contributions:
    - Farmers' Loan and Trust Company, N.Y.:
      - Loans and stocks, 1902-1912
      - Passbook, 1912-1919
    - First Methodist Episcopal Church, Somerville, N.J.:
      - Deeds, 1874, 1919, 1925, 1928
      - 1921-1932, undated, (3 folders)
    - German-American National Bank of New Orleans, 1920-1933
    - Lincoln Hospital: Endowment, 1905
- Estate Series, 1777-1934, and undated (bulk 1926-1928)
  Divided into four subseries: Correspondence, Legal Papers, Financial Papers, and Printed Materials, all pertaining to the administration of the estate of James B. Duke.
  - Correspondence Subseries, 1925-1931, undated
    Chiefly correspondence received and sent by the executors, claimants, attorneys, witnesses, and Benjamin N. Duke. Includes correspondence; some affidavits and other legal documents; and reports. Charles Caldwell's materials filed in the series include correspondence and activity and expense reports. Arranged chronologically.
    - 1925, Oct.-Nov. 30 (3 folders) (Box 24)
    - 1925, Dec.-1926, Apr. (8 folders) (Box 25)
    - 1926, May-Dec. (8 folders) (Box 26)
    - 1927, Jan.-July (7 folders) (Box 27)
    - 1927, Aug.-Dec. 12 (7 folders) (Box 28)
    - 1928, Jan.-Nov. (8 folders) (Box 29)
    - 1930-1931, undated
  - Legal Papers Subseries, 1777-1928, undated (bulk 1925-1928)
    Includes records collected and notes and reports of findings made by Charles Caldwell during the pre-trial period of discovery; notes and legal research by executors and attorneys; reports and correspondence from private investigators and handwriting and other experts, affidavits, completed questionnaires, and related correspondence submitted by claimants; court records including evidence; records for the distribution of the monies under Item VI of the will; and other legal records. See also oversize materials.
    Folders titled Discovery: Charles Caldwell Notes include copies of census and other official records, information about witnesses and evidence, plans for research activities, handwritten copies of affidavits taken by Caldwell, correspondence, lists of prepared questions, and lists of claimants. The majority of census reports, court and county records, wills and inventories, and land deeds in the discovery files are copies; there are also notes taken from the original records in the discovery files. Folders with 1927 enclosed in parentheses indicate that the folder contains only copies or notes from original records and no new information created during the research. Legal research based on other court cases is dated to when the research occurred, not to the date of the original cases.
    Most of the completed forms and affidavits are filed as claims under the name of the alleged common ancestor. Claims were arranged in two categories: allowed and disallowed. Evidence includes correspondence, pages from bibles and other printed materials, legal documents, and memoranda, some are photostatic copies of original documents. It is arranged in two sections according to numbers assigned by the lawyers for the estate. There is a P section (P.1, P.2, etc.) and an E.D. section (E.D.1, E.D.2, etc.) E.D. refers to the evidence in the case against Elizabeth Duke. If evidence has both a P and an E.D. number, the item was filed under P. The index to the evidence was created by the lawyers for the estate.
    Series arranged according to the progress of the settlement of the estate with some legal transfers of funds to organizations first; followed by discovery and research files pertaining to the claims of Elizabeth Duke and the Vaughans, court records and evidence for these claims, documentation of the final determination by the executors, and allowed and disallowed claims (other than Elizabeth Duke and the Vaughans).
    - Nanaline Duke et. al. (executors) v. Southern Power Co. (; Piedmont Electro-Chemical Co.) and Dillworth Methodist Episcopal Church, South, 1923, Oct.-1927, Feb. (3 folders) (Box 30)
      - Cancelled notes transferred in settlement, 1927, Feb.
    - Discovery:
      - Notes on Vaughan claim,; Polly (Mary) Duke Vaughan kinship, ca. 1927
      - Notes on Elizabeth Duke claim, Thomas Duke kinship:
        - (Texas), ca. 1927, June
        - (Ga.) (includes affidavits), 1927, June-July
      - Wills and inventories, 1788-1905 (1927), 1927
      - Court records, 1852-1853 (1927)
      - Records and taxables with notations, 1753-1856 (1927)
      - Court records: Taylor Duke, 1799-1818 (1927)
      - Marriage records and notes: Duke,; Stagg,; Vaughan, 1783-1927
      - Military service: Records and notes: Tillett Harris et. al., 1784 (1927), 1908-1927
      - Land and property deeds and transfers, 1777-1880 (1927), 1927
      - Census returns with correspondence, 1800-1870 (1927), 1927-1928 (2 folders)
    - Discovery: (Box 31)
      - Census returns, 1800-1870 (1927)
      - Census returns: Marked as Ex. A-V, 1810-1870 (1927)
      - Census returns: Notes, ca. 1927-1928
      - Correspondence and reports from expert witnesses, 1928, Jan.-Feb.
      - Report from National Coloniana Society on the descendents of J.B. Duke and disputed claims, 1927, Apr.
      - Notes: Washington Duke, 1927
      - Copy of Determination by the Executors... used by Charles Caldwell, 1927
      - Duke family history, undated
      - Charles Caldwell:
        - Daily Activity Statements, 1927, May 9-Sept. 13
        - Reports, 1927-1928
        - Notes, 1927, June-Nov. (5 folders)
    - Discovery: (Box 32)
      - Charles Caldwell:
        - Notes, 1927, Dec.-1928, May, undated, (5 folders)
        - Expenses and receipts, 1926, July-1928, Mar.,undated
    - Elizabeth Duke claim:
      - Notes about Elizabeth Duke's activities, correspondence, and evidence; used to prepare for direct/cross-examination, 1928, Jan.-May, undated, (3 folders)
      - Notes regarding exhibits, evidence, expert witnesses, and Elizabeth Duke, 1928, Jan. 18-Apr. 26,undated
      - Notes to prepare for trial on March 24 and 25, 1928
      - Notes by Charles Caldwell regarding exhibits and evidence for trial, 1927, Aug. 22-1928, Apr. 28
      - Notes for and correspondence to Senator Case, pertaining to evidence and trial, 1928, Apr. 21
      - Notes about Elizabeth Duke used to prepare for trial, 1928
      - Reports of private investigator on Elizabeth Duke and others, 1927, Nov. 29-Dec. 17
      - Notes on witnesses, 1928, Mar., undated
      - Pretrial conference between lawyers for Estate / Elizabeth Duke, 1927, Nov. 25 (transcript)
      - Notes on testimonies and affidavits of Dr. Henry M. Duke and others, 1928, Jan. 20
      - Notes on testimonies and affadavits of John T. and Frances E. Eady, 1928, Jan. 23-24
      - Notes on testimonies, 1928, Jan. 23-31 (2 folders)
      - Notes on testimony and affidavits of Hattie Gaffield, 1928, Jan. 26
      - Notes on transcript of testimony, pp. 569-1120, 1928, Jan. 25-31
      - Notes from testimonies, 1928, Mar. 15-16; notes in preparation for Mar. 16
    - Elizabeth Duke claim: (Box 33)
      - Notes from testimony with Charles Caldwell's notes made during trial, 1928, Mar. 19-22
      - Notes from testimony by W. R. Perkins, including notes on evidence, 1928, Mar. 22-26
      - Pre-trial records: Interrogatories, 1928, Apr.
      - Notes on testimonies of George G. Allen,; August Harkhorn,; Stewart L. Hawkins,; C.E. Mapes, 1928, May 21
      - Notes on testimonies, undated
      - Names of claimants presenting claims through E. Duke, 1927
      - Charles Duke kinship (Ga.), 1928
      - David Duke kinship (Ga. and Miss.), 1926-1928
      - David and Thomas Duke kinship and affiliation with Primitive Baptist Church, affidavits, 1927
      - David Duke kinship, 1927
      - Robert Duke kinship, 1926
      - Thomas Duke kinship:
        - affidavits, 1926-1928 (6 folders)
        - (Primitive Baptist), affidavits and evidence, 1927
        - (Primitive Baptist), affidavits and interviews, 1927
      - Misc. affidavits, 1926-1928
      - Affidavits relating to her evidence, 1927-1928
    - Vaughan claim:
      - List of descendants, undated
      - Executor's questionnaires and affidavits (disallowed claims), 1925-1927 (2 folders)
      - Statement by Eugene Lee Vaughan, 1926, June 22
      - Statement of evidence submitted by E.L. Vaughan, 1926, Oct. 18
      - Evidence submitted by E.L. Vaughan, 1926
    - Vaughan claim: (Box 34)
      - Statement on behalf of E.L. Vaughan, setting forth the grounds of his claim, with affidavits, 1927, Apr. 18 (2 folders)
      - Recapitulation of the facts on which E.L. Vaughan bases his claim, 1927, May 5
      - Notes about claims and evidence, undated
      - Affidavits, A-W, 1925-1927, undated, (3 folders)
      - Tillett Harris's affidavits, records of questioning, pension records, 1927, undated
      - Last will and testament of James Vaughan ( 1788, Oct. 26), undated
    - Legal research: Precedents, ca. 1927
    - On Petition for Decree of Distribution of $2 million under Item VI of [ J.B. Duke's] Will, Decree of Distribution, 1927, Nov.
    - On Petition for Decree: Order of Adjournment, 1927, Nov. 25
    - On Petition of Edward Lee Vaughan for reopening case, etc.; Order, 1928, Jan. 6
    - On Petition for Decree: Order, 1928, Jan. 6
    - On Petition of Decree of Distribution: Order, 1928, May 21
    - Transcript of Trial: On Petition for Decree, 1928, Jan. 6-20 (3 folders)
    - Transcript of Trial: On Petition for Decree: 1928, Jan. 23-31; Mar. 15-16 (2 vols., 3 folders) (Box 35)
    - Transcript of Trial: On Petition for Decree, 1928, Mar. 16-26 (7 folders, 1 vol.) (Box 36)
    - Index to evidence, 1928 (Box 37)
    - Evidence (P series):
      - P. 1-2, undated
      - P. 3, 6-40, 1926-1928,undated
      - P. 41-60, 1866-1928,undated
      - P. 61-81, 1801-1928
      - P. 82-91, 95-96, 1861-1928,undated
      - P. 98, 1894-1928
      - P. 100, undated
      - P. 102-123, 1861-1928,undated
      - P. 130-140, 1861-1928,undated
      - P. 141-159, 161, 1866-1928,undated
    - Evidence (P series): (Box 38)
      - P. 126-129, 1928
      - P. 160, pp. 1-38, 1928 (3 folders)
    - Evidence: pages from church books (photographs and photostats), 1928
    - Evidence (E.D. series):
      - E.D. 1-5, 1928
      - E.D. 6, 7, 20, 26, 1928
      - E.D. 13-14, 18-19, 21-23, 1928
    - Determination by the Executors of James B. Duke, Deceased, of Those Entitled to Participate in the Distribution Made Under Item VI.. ., 1927 (Box 39)
    - Determination by Executors:
      - Final awards, ca. 1926-1928
      - Schedule of Disallowed Claims, ca. 1927-1928
    - List of affidavits received by Executors, undated
    - Claims (allowed):
      - Duke, John Taylor:
        - (Executors' questionnaires), 1927
        - James A. Duke,; Martha Angeline Duke Moore ( affidavits), 1926
        - Lida Duke Angier,; Pattie Duke Moore ( affidavits), 1926-1928
        - Nannie Duke Wyant,; Maude Duke Karnes Stuart ( affidavits), 1926-1927
        - John T. Duke,; Lillie I. Duke ( affidavits), 1926
      - Duke, Robert:
        - Andrew J. Duke,; Charles Washington Duke,; Eliza Annie Duke (Evans)
        - Robert A. Duke ( questionnaires and affidavits), 1926-1928
      - Duke, William J.:
        - (Executors' questionnaires), 1927
        - James McCadden Duke,; William Kirkland Duke, Price (Luena Duke Price) (affidavits), 1926-1927
        - Holloway,; Patterson,; Lyon ( affidavits), 1925-1928
    - Claims (allowed): (Box 40)
      - Riggs, Amelia Frances Duke, 1925-1927
      - Stagg, Mary Duke, 1926-1928
      - Roney, (Fonville, Catherine Roney):
        - (Executors' questionnaires), 1927
        - (affidavits), 1925-1928 (2 folders)
      - Roney, Amos K. ( Executors' questionnaires, affidavits), 1926-1927
      - Roney, Benjamin F.:
        - (Executors' questionnaires), 1927
        - (affidavits), 1925-1926 (2 folders)
      - Roney, Calvin Newton Duke ( Executors' questionnaires, affidavits), 1925-1927
      - Roney, Henry C.:
        - (Executors' questionnaires), 1927
        - (affidavits), 1925-1926 (2 folders)
      - Roney, John T. ( Executors' questionnaires, affidavits), 1926-1927
    - Claims (disallowed): (Box 41)
      - Clinton, Mary, 1926-1927
      - Duke, Alfred Lee, 1925-1927
      - Duke, Clevarious, 1926-1927
      - Duke, Daniel ( Va.), 1926-1927
      - Duke, David Washington, 1927
      - Duke, Edmund, 1926-1927
      - Duke, Francis Kirkland, 1927
      - Duke, James, (; Sarah E. Duke Osborn), 1926-1927
      - Duke, James, ( Va. and W. Va.), 1926-1927
      - Duke, James ( W. Va.), 1927
      - Duke, James P. ( La. and Ala.), 1926-1927
      - Duke, John Taylor:
        - Walter Lewis Duke ( problem of), 1929
        - Grief Duke ( problem of), includes Duke,; Latta,; Garrard,; Proctor (questionnaires and affidavits), 1925-1927
      - Duke, Joseph, 1926-1927
      - Duke, Llewellyn/Robert, 1925-1927
      - Duke, Mary Elizabeth, 1926-1927
      - Duke, Polly, 1927
      - Duke, Reany (Reny), 1927-1928
      - Duke, Robert, 1926-1927
      - Duke, Samuel ( N.C.), 1925, undated
      - Duke, Tyre or Noah, 1925-1927
      - Duke, William ( Indiana), 1927
      - Duke, William (; Durell Mangum), 1927
      - Duke, William ( Va. and Ohio), 1898-1927, (2 folders)
      - Duke, William ( Va. and Tenn.), 1856-1927 (2 folders)
      - Duke, William, 1925-1927
    - Claims (disallowed): (Box 42)
      - Duke, William J., 1926-1927
      - Duke, William Edmund, 1927
      - Duke, William J., 1926-1927
      - Duke, William J. ( N.C.), 1926-1927
      - Duke, William J.; (Polly Duke Hardin), 1926-1927
      - Duke, William J. ( Warren County, N.C.), 1926-1927
      - Duke William Joseph, 1927
      - Jacobs, Malinda Duke, 1926-1927
      - Roney, 1925-1927 (2 folders)
      - Roney (Trollinger), 1926-1927 (2 folders)
    - Claims: Miscellaneous (Executors' questionnaires and affidavits), 1872-1927
    - Item VI Beneficiaries: Assignments:
      - Angier, John, 1926
      - Clute, Grover V., 1928
      - Clute, John H., 1928
      - Fonville, Gabriel L., 1928
      - Garrison, Barbara, 1927-1928
      - Jones, Sallie Colbino, 1927-1928
      - Lyon, W.F., 1927
      - Moore, Martha Ann, 1927-1928
      - Park, Marlowe Roney, 1927
      - Riggs, Frances, 1926-1928
      - Stagg, William L., 1927-1928
      - Wood, Joseph M., 1926-1928
    - Item VI Beneficiaries: Attachment by the Court of share for Mrs. W.H. (Roxie) Foushee (; Wilkinson v. Foushee), 1928-1929
    - Item VI Beneficiaries: Guardianship:
      - Barton, Essie Lee and Jessie May, 1923-1927
      - Bowden, Alice M., 1927-1928
      - Dailey, John Calvin and Lucille Park, 1927
      - Davis, Henry W., Stanley W., and Montrose J., 1927-1928
      - Duke, Charles W., 1927-1928
      - Fonville, Ralph W. and Raymond E., 1927-1928
      - Holloway, Clarence R., Hallie, Reba, and J. Earl, 1927-1928
      - Patterson, Victor Hugo, Maurine, and Elbert Earle, 1927-1928
    - Item VI Beneficiaries: Guardianship: (Box 43)
      - Price, William N., 1927-1928
      - Roney, Mildred, 1927-1928
      - Rowland, Mary Florence and Annie Elizabeth, 1924-1928
      - Wilson, Walter A. and Doris A., 1927-1928
    - Receipts for Legacy and Refunding Bonds, 1926-1934 (4 folders)
    - Receipts for Covering Specific Bequests (A-P), 1927-1929, (8 folders)
    - Receipts covering specific bequests (R-Z), 1927-1929, (3 folders) (Box 44)
    - Order Allowing Final Account, 1934, June 15; Petition on Final Accounting with schedules, 1934, Apr. 26
    - Petition on First Accounting with schedules, 1926, Dec. 31
  - Financial Papers Subseries, 1925-1934
    Includes final accounting work papers for the estate, a ledger book, journal, cashbooks, trial balances, analysis of income, statements of income, voucher records, vouchers and receipts, and income tax returns. Inventories of Mr. Duke's personal properties are filed under Receipts for Legacy and Refunding Bonds, 1926. Receipts for specific bequests are filed alphabetically by recipient name. Arranged with the estate's final accounting work papers first (related to Order Allowing Final Account); followed by volumes and records in descending order according to the hierarchy of the bookkeeping system, miscellaneous bookkeeping records, subject files, and banking records. Vouchers and receipts are arranged into categories (schedules of accounting) ascribed by the executors.
    - Final Accounting work papers, 1925-1934
    - Final Accounting work papers, 1934-1937 (Box 45)
    - Statements of Distribution of the Estate, 1926-1934
    - Ledger, 1925-1934
    - Journal, 1925, Oct. 11-1934, June
    - Cashbook, 1925, Oct. 16-1932, Sept. 30
    - Cashbook, 1932, Oct. 1-1934, June 18 (Box 46)
    - Voucher Records:
      - No. 1, 1925, Oct.-1930, Apr.
      - No. 2, 1930, May-1934, June
    - Miscellaneous bookkeeping:
      - Trial Balances, 1925-1934 (10 folders)
      - Analyses of Income, 1925-1928
      - Statements of Income, 1929, June-Dec.
      - Bonds owned by J.B. Duke on 1925, Oct. 10
      - Stocks and bonds, 1925-1933
      - Inventory of office furniture at 535 Fifth Ave., New York City, ca. 1934
    - Check stubs: (Box 47)
      - National Bank of Commerce, 1925, Oct. 11-1913, Sept. 28
      - The National City Bank of New York, 1925, Oct. 11-1928, Feb. 1
    - Cancelled checks:
      - National Bank of Commerce, N.Y., 1925-1928, Sept. 13
      - The National City Bank of N.Y., 1925-1928, Sept. 13
    - Vouchers and receipts, Administration expenses, 1926, Dec.-1928, Mar. (10 folders)
    - Vouchers and receipts, Administration expenses, 1928, Apr.-1930, May (15 folders) (Box 48)
    - Vouchers and receipts, Administration expenses, 1930, June-1933, June (15 folders) (Box 49)
    - Vouchers and receipts: (Box 50)
      - Administration expenses, 1933, July-1934, June (5 folders)
      - Bonds/securities delivered to trustees of The Duke Endowment,; Trust for Doris Duke, and others, 1928-1933
      - Investments and exchanges, 1926-1931
      - Property sold, 1927-1931
      - Expenses paid from income, 1927-1933
      - Collection charges, 1926-1934, (5 folders)
      - Taxes, 1927-1934
      - Debts of decedent, 1927
    - Vouchers and receipts: (Box 51)
      - Inheritance taxes, 1926-1933
      - Executors' fees, 1927-1929
      - Liquidation of accounts payable, 1926-1931
      - Residuary bequests, 1927-1934
      - Distribution of income, 1927-1934
      - Miscellaneous, 1927-1931
    - Bank advices:
      - Bankers Trust Company,; Farmers' Loan and Trust Company,; Guaranty Trust Company of New York,; National Bank of Commerce in New York, 1926
      - Bankers Trust Company, 1927
      - Farmers Loan and Trust Co., 1927
      - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1927
      - National City Bank of New York, 1927
      - National Bank of Commerce in New York, 1927
      - Bankers Trust Co., 1928
      - Farmers Loan and Trust Co., 1928
      - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1928
      - National Bank of Commerce in New York, 1928
      - National City Bank of New York, 1928
      - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1929
      - National Bank of Commerce in New York; (Bank of Commerce in New York), 1929
      - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1930
    - Bank advices: (Box 52)
      - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1931-1934, Apr. (4 folders)
    - Passbooks: Central Union Trust Company, 1926-1930; Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1927-1928
    - Check stubs:
      - Bankers Trust Company, 1925, Nov. 5-1928, Oct. 4